but the standout brokerage reports are
in focus with NES who standing by nes
good morning hi morning prashan today's
Stand Out is on icsl Lombard City
interestingly has initiated a sell on
the on the stock with a Target price of
1575 a potential 69% downside from
current levels uh City believes that
while the company's multiproduct model
Diversified distribution footprint uh
robust underwriting and strong parentage
supports uh the steady growth and
profitability however some uh risk and
some you know headwinds are emerging for
the company which include dis
disproportionately high and Swift
increase in the B2B business which can
be which can lead to higher lumpy and
adoc risk and further Rising competition
which means and there's there's also
reducing you know distribution mode in
the retail segment so these are the few
few risk for for the company going
forward while uh elevated investment
income in the near term can support the
near-term Outlook but there are now
concerns over the profitability over the
longer term which is ignored by the
current market at this Rich valuation so
while they've put out some upset risk as
well which includes moderation in the
retail competition as well as you know
better experience in the B2B business
but this a risk for the company going
forward and H and initiating sell on
icsl Lombard with a Target price of 1575
a potential 600% downset from current
levels okay so that's um that's a call
that really stands out a big sell on IC
Lombard got that thanks very much for it
NES